[Music]
This information is only our opinion and
not financial advice. Please do your own research before making any decision.
We are not responsible for any profit or loss.
Let's take a look
at today's blog deals. Total shares of ICICI Lord General
Insurance Company Limited KUM
200 were bought by Aditya Birla Sun Life
Mutual Fund which were
bought by Bhartiya Enterprises Limited at the mentioned price and the trader category
is 172.5. The trader belongs to the public category.
This was today's major mutual fund
deals. Thanks for watching.
Subscribe to the channel for latest stock news updates
and like and share the video.